♪
Oh.
Hey, Suzuki! What's up?
Oh, hey, good morning, Azuma!
[AZUMA] Is that the yeti
from that new movie?
Uh-huh! My little fluffball.
So, who'd you see it with?
You go with Nabe or Satou?
No, uh...
with Tani.
[AZUMA] Hm?
- Tani? Why'd he go with you?
- [Suzuki muttering]
- Mmm... Mmm...
- 'Cause we're dating.
- What? And you didn't tell me?
- Oopsies, my b!
That's all you have to say,
"my b?"
Start talking.
When did this happen?
Recently.
And how did this happen?
- Uh, well.
- Who asked who out?
It was, uh...
[gasps] Blackmail?
[SUZUKI] Are you ever
gonna let me talk, or...
Oh, my God, girl.
- Oh, my God...
- Are you happy
or about to have a breakdown?
The former.
But I'm also, like,
insanely jealous right now.
The two of you are so sweet,
it is making me physically ill.
Thanks I guess?
Hey, why are you
so calm right now?
Are you not freaking out?
You're confused.
Tani's the calm one.
Wait, serious people attract
serious people.
Are you a serious person?
How did I not notice?
Is my whole life a lie?
[SUZUKI] Um, are you good?
Yeah, just wish I could find
a guy who has it together.
My last ex totally ghosted me
with absolutely
zero warning one day.
But then I found out
it was 'cause he got thrown
into juvie, so, yeah.
Wouldn't exactly say
it was my finest hour.
But whatever, that's just love.
Girly, that is not "just love."
[YAMADA] You see any
good movies lately, Taira?
Nah, I don't like
theater crowds.
They're either too loud
or too quiet, no in-between.
[YAMADA] Funny, Gapacho said
the same thing.
But the new one
with the witch
and the fluffy guy
might be worth the risk!
- That's what you wanna see?
- [SUZUKI] Come on now,
don't give up!
- What if the right person's...
- Here comes Suzuki.
I know that screech.
Nah, unfortunately,
I've got a type
and it's toxic tools
across the board.
I meet someone,
I think he's the one,
boom... psychopath.
Heavy stuff.
We just got here.
It's never too early
to lift up our friends
and help them find romance!
Come on, Azuma, tell him!
Maybe dying alone
is what I deserve
for finding good people unsexy.
[YAMADA] Oh, my God,
I think you broke her.
I told you, girls love a rebel.
There's something
about a rap sheet
that makes them go crazy.
It's science.
We get it, no one wanted
to date you in middle school.
Now hold on. Is the man wrong?
Dudes who are rough
around the edges are so hot!
They've got that "I'm damaged,
fix me" rizz,
you know what I mean?
[AZUMA] You are down
horrendous for SudaKen.
- [Suzuki chuckles]
- [TAIRA] Dating is all about
climbing up
the social hierarchy.
It doesn't matter
what's on the inside,
it's about finding a partner
who can raise your position.
[TAIRA] People want
someone at the top
of the attractiveness
pecking order.
And once they land
that someone,
it boosts them up
a few rungs themselves.
[SUZUKI] SudaKen,
my bodacious...
- [TAIRA] It's all so stupid.
- Better get the squirt bottle.
Hey, Suzuki,
should you be saying that?
I mean, Tani's right there.
[screams]
- Tani, hi, how's your desk?
- [Watanabe and Yamada laugh]
- Hello.
- [SATOU] Damage control mode.
So, hey, uh, did you hear
our whole convo?
Yes, I heard it all,
but nothing you said
bothered me.
Look at her, she's so cute
when she's spiraling.
Everybody shut up,
my show is on.
Here we go.
Hey, am I missing something?
Oh.
Yeah, those guys
are a couple now.
[TAIRA] Huh?
Wait, how come everyone else
is acting normal?
Nobody finds this weird?
Maybe they reacted differently
when they first found out.
- Are you okay?
- [TAIRA] Someone must've
grabbed her by the shoulders
and screamed "Why him," right?
He really doesn't seem
like her type.
[SUZUKI] SudaKen,
be still my heart!
[SUZUKI] I want a dangerous,
dominant...
[TAIRA] The gap between
her fantasy
and her reality
is a million miles wide.
[SUZUKI]
...beefcake chorus line.
Greetings, my dude.
How's it hangin'?
[TANI] Good morning.
[TAIRA] And why's Yamada
acting like the two of them
are lifelong friends?
- Whoa! A fluffy!
- [Suzuki exclaiming]
OMG, we match!
- I smell a waft of love stank!
- [TANI] Love stank?
Oh, that reminds me,
did you take any pics?
Uh, no, what even are those?
- Okay, liar.
- We took one.
Et tu, Tani?
- Hey, I wanna see!
- [WATANABE] Show me! Show me!
[TAIRA] What is happening
to the world?
[♪ opening theme song playing]
[Taira groans]
It's so hot today.
I need a drink.
Uh?
Are you trying
to beat the heat too?
[TAIRA] Hey, Suzuki.
You're out of luck if you wanted
a Reality Gold Strong.
Your girl just
cleaned them all out.
[TAIRA] Have at it.
I don't drink that garbage.
Oh, but the fizzies.
Hey, tell me something.
[SUZUKI] Mm?
- Why'd you pick Tani?
- [gasps]
My first love triangle!
What? Good lord, no.
What is wrong with you?
I just don't understand it.
It'd be one thing if Yamada
or Watanabe dated
someone like him.
Those two don't give
a crap. But you?
You're obsessed with
what everyone thinks of you.
Oh, my God. Is that what
everyone thinks of me?
And yet, you're dating someone
on the opposite wavelength.
It's weird.
[Suzuki chuckles]
[SUZUKI] Yeah, you're right
that I always worry
about what others think.
I work my butt off to fit in
and drive myself crazy
wondering if people like me.
But, hey, maybe that explains
why I ended up
going for someone like Tani.
I'm a peeps pleaser,
whereas Tani is strictly himself
no matter what the peeps think.
Uh... oops,
word vomit.
You really have to hear
the whole story
to get why I'm like this.
You got a couple hours?
[TAIRA] Only if you've got
a cyanide capsule for me.
[Suzuki laughs]
[TANI] This window seat's
frying me alive.
[Tani gasps]
Heya!
[chuckles] I've always wanted
to do that to someone!
Were you shooketh?
Yes, I was.
You don't look shooketh.
[TAIRA] Seriously,
they're already doing
stereotypical couple things?
I bought us drinks to cool off,
which one do you want?
Papa or baby?
[TAIRA] Why'd she get
two of the same thing?
- [TANI] Baby, please.
- [TAIRA] Ah, how chivalrous.
How much was it?
You don't need
to pay me back, silly!
Oh, you sure?
Of course I am. Come on,
do I look that broke?
[TAIRA] And now
I'm eavesdropping on them
- like a total chud.
- [SUZUKI] But if you insist,
- three yen!
- [TANI] I don't need a discount.
[Taira groans]
[TAIRA] Aren't they
just two peas in a pod?
[screams]
So how was
your drink pilgrimage?
- What the eff?
- I accidentally left my water
in the freezer for too long,
so now I'm bashin' it
to try and get it to thaw out.
Can you test out Mjolnir
somewhere else, please?
[YAMADA] Suzuki!
What do you want now?
Homework, please!
You're so lame!
Do your own homework.
This is getting stupid.
[cries]
- Tani?
- Don't you dare!
Are you sure you don't wanna
take a look at mine?
I mean, I have already
completed the assignment.
[TAIRA] Oh, great, now they're
gonna exploit the poor guy
for his intelligence?
Just know you won't learn
anything this way,
okay?
I can live with that.
[SUZUKI] Well, I can't!
Hands off, you little leech!
[TAIRA] Suzuki really
does like Tani.
That much is obvious.
Everyone understands
it's her choice,
so they're just cool with it.
- Leave him alone, dude!
- Give it here, bestie!
[overlapping chatter]
[TAIRA]
They're not even worried
about what other people
will think.
You can take your sob story
and shove it up your blowhole!
Dude, get off!
[TAIRA]
Wait, maybe that's it.
[bell chimes]
[TAIRA] I was so sure
I'd never get it,
but I think I kinda do.
Nice. I'll have to
check them out!
[TAIRA]
It really messed me up
to see someone I considered
an afterthought
suddenly getting accepted
into the group,
just like that.
I assumed he must have
compromised
who he was
to get their approval.
But the truth is,
not everyone fixates on what
other people say and do
or obsesses over their rank
in the social hierarchy.
That's just me.
And I've made it
my whole personality.
[AZUMA] Um?
You okay there, Taira?
[AZUMA] Uh?
[TAIRA] People who know
who they are don't change
because of what others do.
They retain their
own independent identity.
I am my own prisoner,
shackled to the social ladder.
Whoa, okay,
I think I'm gonna go.
Whoa! Howdy-do, TairAzuma!
[AZUMA] Please don't ship
real people.
You lovebirds
walking home together?
Yeap!
Hasta mañana!
Okay, see you tomorrow!
[TAIRA]
They're so shameless,
walking side by side like that.
Like they couldn't care less
who sees them.
Kind of inspiring.
Maybe it's time
I had a reinvention arc.
Didn't you just have one,
like, two years ago?
No, shut up.
[Suzuki humming]
- Listen, Suzuki.
- [SUZUKI] Hm?
I've been thinking,
if there's
a certain kind of person
that you're attracted to,
then I should try to become
that kind of person.
That said,
I need you to understand
that I won't be doing
- anything unethical.
- Huh?
Dudes who are rough around
the edges are so hot.
They've got that "I'm damaged,
fix me" rizz, know what I mean?
[Suzuki gasps]
I knew you were
bothered by that!
I'm not bothered by it.
Quit pretending.
If it really didn't bother you,
then you wouldn't have
brought it up!
It's fine. Like I said.
You lie!
[Suzuki laughing]
What now?
Why do you seem happy?
Forget it. [laughs]
- Okay, I'll tell you.
- [sighs]
Tani, I like all kinds of people
for all kinds of reasons.
Especially you.
I get it, it's okay.
I get butterflies in my stomach
if someone looks cool,
or acts cool,
or has a cool personality.
But everyone's
a different kind of cool,
you know what I mean, jellybean?
Yes, I think I do.
That face you're making
is so adorable!
You just keep getting cuter.
- [TANI] Hm?
- It's kinda hard to describe.
But who we like
comes from our own
personal coolness code!
[humming]
You couldn't be
any more adorable!
Daw, Tani!
Uh, Suzuki?
What do you mean by "adorable"?
[distorted]
Cute, tiny Tani.
All for me!
- [Tani groans]
- [TEMPURA] Meow.
- Meow. Meow.
- [TANI] I can't breathe.
- [Tani gasps]
- [meows]
[yawns]
[Tani breathes heavily]
Morning. You got up early.
[TANI] Tempura was on my face.
Oh, my, Tempura,
you adorable little rascal.
[Tempura meows]
Dudes who are rough around
the edges are so hot.
They've got that
"I'm damaged, fix me" rizz.
I like all kinds of people
for all kinds of reasons.
[meows]
[TANI] I told her
it didn't bother me,
but what exactly does
Suzuki find attractive?
Is it strength?
If it is, then I...
[TANI] Mm...
- [TANI] Too heavy.
- [meows]
[SUZUKI] Come on, don't hog it!
Get your giant butt
out of my way.
I've been waiting
a million hours!
Back off, freak!
[both grunting]
[SUZUKI] Mom, where did you
put my gym clothes?
- I'm gonna be late!
- I won't be home tonight,
- I don't need any dinner!
- One at a time, please.
I only have two ears!
Give me a ride halfway!
[SUZUKI'S BROTHER]
What the hell? Get off!
[motorbike approaching]
[SUZUKI] Whoa there, horsie!
Stop right there!
[SUZUKI'S BROTHER]
I am not your horse! Get lost.
[Suzuki laughing]
[sighs] Thanks times a milly!
[TANI] Huh?
♪
Kind of uncharacteristically
gnarly for her.
Don't you think?
I guess.
Where'd she come from?
[Tani sighs]
[Azuma sighs]
Let me guess,
you have no idea who that guy
on the bike with her was.
- I don't.
- Hmm.
Hey, hairball!
Oh, Az...
Tani! [gasps]
Why are you guys here together
at the worst possible time?
[AZUMA]
Good morning to you too.
So, was that your
older brother just now?
- [SUZUKI] Yeah. Gross, right?
- [TANI] Huh?
Motorcycles are so sexy.
Can you introduce me to him?
First of all, no,
second of all,
your taste is awful.
Back me up here, Tani.
Please don't involve me
in this discussion.
[laughs]
- Feel better now?
- [Tani sighs]
Come to think of it,
do you have any siblings, Tani?
[TANI] I don't.
[BOTH] Yeah, checks out.
[TANI] Why did they act
like they expected that?
[AZUMA] So, Suzuki,
does your brother
have a girlfriend?
[SUZUKI] No idea,
but even if he doesn't,
- I'm not gonna give his number.
- [TAIRA] Pigs have flown.
[AZUMA] Aww.
[bell chimes]
[SUZUKI] Time to make
like a tree and leave!
- You go ahead.
- [SUZUKI] Huh?
I'm a library assistant,
so I have to stay and work.
Aw, you never told me that.
No worries,
I'll be fine on my own.
[TANI] Well,
that wasn't convincing.
[Suzuki hums suspiciously]
[GIRL] Hm?
[GIRL] Huh?
[TANI] Hello?
- Suzuki?
- [gasps]
Are you all right?
Oh, yeah, just checkin' out
some, uh, literature.
I realized I've never really
used the library, like, ever.
Isn't that crazy?
I was just waiting
for you to wrap up
and I thought I'd come
look at all these cool books.
Oh, sorry, I'm acting
like such a stalker.
[TANI] I don't think
you are at all.
Really? Oh, thank God.
[TANI] Actually,
if I'm being honest,
I'm happy to see her.
Oh, maybe I should have
told her that just now!
But I don't want her to
wait around for me too long.
Suzuki, you can go if you want.
There isn't much for you
to do here.
[Suzuki gasps]
[TANI] Uh?
Do you think I can't read?
Oh, God, he thinks
I can't read.
No, that isn't
what I meant, I just...
Don't you worry about me!
I'll just grab a book real quick
and head home for today.
[SUZUKI] I get it.
It's annoying having someone
hanging around
when you're working.
Like, when friends show up
to your part-time job
and you can't decide
between being buddy, buddy,
or professional.
[TANI] I messed up.
I thought I was
being considerate,
but she didn't take it
that way.
[TANI] Suzuki.
[SUZUKI] Huh? Oh...
[TANI] The library is going
to close at five o'clock.
Wait for me?
[Suzuki gasps]
Hmm. Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[chuckles]
♪
[girl gasps]
[girl breathes uneasily]
♪
[TANI] Up until now,
I went through life
taking things people said
to me literally.
Completely missing everything
under the surface.
It didn't matter to me
if my intentions
were conveyed properly
through my words.
I never gave it
a second thought.
Expressing
my thoughts verbally
and understanding others
hoping to do the same
is difficult to figure out.
I can't help but worry
that there's still
a lot I'm missing.
[Suzuki humming]
[SUZUKI] Hey, Gomapon!
Are you headed home
right now, too?
Well, what does it look like?
[SUZUKI] Whoa, nice e-bike,
very compact! [laughs]
Don't laugh at me.
Go home before it gets dark.
Damn kids.
Okay, bye!
- Sorry, were you waiting long?
- [exclaims]
[Suzuki laughs]
I just saw
Gomapon leaving school
on the teeniest little
baby bike! [laughs]
What's so strange about that?
Watching him fried me!
The bike was way too tiny
for his not-tiny body!
The wheels looked like
little biscuits!
The whole thing was
so adorable, I was dying!
[TANI] There it is again.
Quick question.
When you see something
and say that it's "adorable,"
what do you mean?
Huh? You don't know?
Not exactly.
I understand how you might find
a kitten or a panda adorable,
but when it comes
to our faculty members
and their vehicles,
I don't quite follow.
Oh, now I see.
Huh, what's a better way
for me to describe it?
I guess it's sort of like
getting my heart squeezed,
but in a sweet and happy way?
Oh!
It's endearing!
Does that make any more sense?
♪
I guess guys don't toss
around the word "adorable"
all that much, huh?
Later!
I'll have to keep going
to the library from now on!
The book I got
is part of a series!
Oh, I've actually read
that one too.
Really? Once I'm done,
we can talk about it!
Oh, maybe you could recommend
some big brain books
for me to read!
Really? You want me to?
Yeah! I mean,
our tastes are probably
totally different. [giggles]
But that's still fun!
I mean, it's not like
we need to be
carbon copies
of each other, right?
The way I see it,
we'll keep on getting
to know each other, bit by bit.
Then when one of us says,
"Yo, I like this,"
the other can say,
"Yeah, I know you do."
I wanna know all the
little things about you.
- Suzuki, I...
- Hm?
[Suzuki gasps]
[TANI] I don't think
I can ever be like SudaKen
or perfectly fit your
"coolness code,"
but...
[Suzuki exclaims]
[Suzuki gasps]
You're adorable.
[Suzuki exclaims]
Do you understand?
[Suzuki speaking gibberish]
[TANI] Okay,
I'll see you tomorrow.
[SUZUKI] Okie-dokie.
[meows]
[Suzuki exclaiming]
Oh, Tani.
What's up, my guy?
Good morning.
- Listen, Tani.
- [TANI] Mm?
I talked to Suzuki earlier,
and I asked her the reason
she picked you.
Dude, come on,
what is your damage?
She said she likes
how you don't change
who you are for other people.
Oh.
What in the hell
do you mean, "oh?"
It's just...
why would you go out
of your way to tell me?
[TAIRA] Huh?
Because the best compliments
are the ones people give
when you're not around
to hear them. Are you stupid?
♪
You know, I think I'd rather be
around to hear them.
No, no, dude,
people totally glaze you
when they tell you nice things
to your face,
everyone knows that!
They say how they really feel
in the darkness,
where you won't see
the knife coming.
Speaking of darkness,
tone it down, man.
Wait a second.
Were you just trying
to cheer Tani up?
Doesn't that go against
your whole misanthrope thing?
Taira,
- you're a really good person.
- [Taira gasps]
What did you
just call me, you freak?
I am a disgusting
cesspool of negativity,
and while trying to clear
the rot from my soul,
I said something nice,
that does not make me
a good person!
Wow, that was a lot.
Is that a new manga?
[SUZUKI] No, girl, it's a book!
When's the last time
you even read a boo...
- Oh?
- What?
[SATOU] That's a weird combo.
[WATANABE] Super weird.
I cut her off before
she stole two hours...
- [SUZUKI] Huh?
- [SATOU] "Huh" indeed.
Tani's actually
smiling for once.
- That's a new one.
- [Suzuki stuttering]
But why?
This isn't happening.
Does he think those guys
are funnier than me?
That's the part
you're worried about?
[♪ closing theme song playing]